



emanuelepanesi@gmail.com



34 648530327



github.com/lele87



www.linkedin.com/in/emanuelepanesi-frontend-developer



























SKILLS

- Determination
- Active learning
- Teamwork skills
- Problem solving skills
- Honesty
- Collaboration

LANGUAGES

- Spanish: Advanced
- English: Intermediate -Advanced
- Italian: Native

EMANUELE PANESI

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

I'm a Full-Stack Developer skilled in developing and testing multiple web-based applications, incorporating a range of technologies. I'm dedicated to programming after leading two companies for the last 10 years that have given me valuable experience leading teams, managing responsibilities and making decisions.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full-Stack Developer & Founder

PIZZADVISOR - BARCELONA 06/2022 - PRESENT

Full - stack responsive App to create and share the best pizzerias in Barcelona. Frontend developed with React and Typescript, managing states with Redux and styles with Styled-Components. The backend uses MongoDB's data model with Mongoose. I deployed a REST API with its corresponding endpoints, using NodeJs y ExpressJs. Tested with Jest and Cypress. Constantly checked with SonarCloud, always following good practices (S.O.L.I.D. principles) with a clean and scalable code

Owner

FOCACCERIA TOSCANA - BARCELONA 05/2011 - 10/2021

- Work team management
- · Employee management and interviews
- · Economic management of the company
- Ability of working under high pressure

Owner

GELATERIA DIVINO - BARCELONA 06/2018 - 06/2021

- Work team management
- · Employee management and interviews
- Economic management of the company
- Ability of working under high pressure

EDUCATION

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

ISDI CODERS

BARCELONA 04/2022 - 06/2022

11 weeks Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp (+ 900h) and final project CRUD with MERN

Technologies:

- Frontend: HTML | CSS | SASS | Bootstrap | BEM | React | Redux | Flux | Typescript | Jest | Cypress | NextJS
- Backend: NodeJS | ExpressJS | MongoDB | Mongoose | Postman
- Other technologies: Git | GitHub | SonarCloud | Lighthouse | EsLint | Trello | Figma